export const data = [
  {
    question: 'What is the polite particle for male speaker?',
    optionOne: 'Krap',
    optionTwo: 'Krep',
    optionThree: 'Ka',
    optionFour: 'Krop',
    answer: 'Krap'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the polite particle for female speaker?',
    optionOne: 'Krip',
    optionTwo: 'Ka',
    optionThree: 'Krap',
    optionFour: 'Krop',
    answer: 'Ka'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say I for male speaker?',
    optionOne: 'Chan',
    optionTwo: 'Pom',
    optionThree: 'Pen',
    optionFour: 'Chon',
    answer: 'Pom'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say I for female speaker?',
    optionOne: 'Pen',
    optionTwo: 'Pom',
    optionThree: 'Pin',
    optionFour: 'Chon',
    answer: 'Chan'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say hello?',
    optionOne: 'Aloha',
    optionTwo: 'Sawatdii',
    optionThree: 'Sawa',
    optionFour: 'Mai',
    answer: 'Sawatdii'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say thank you?',
    optionOne: 'Quack kun',
    optionTwo: 'Kawp kun',
    optionThree: 'Gracias',
    optionFour: 'Kiitos',
    answer: 'Kawp kun'
  },
  {
    question: "How to say you're welcome or my pleasure?",
    optionOne: 'Chai',
    optionTwo: 'Yin dii',
    optionThree: 'Dai',
    optionFour: 'Mai',
    answer: 'Yin dii'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say sorry or excuse me?',
    optionOne: 'Kraw-leo',
    optionTwo: 'Kaw-toot',
    optionThree: 'Kaw-mai',
    optionFour: 'Kaw-krap',
    answer: 'Kaw-toot'
  },
  {
    question: "How to say it's ok or no problem?",
    optionOne: 'Mai bpen rai',
    optionTwo: 'Mai leo',
    optionThree: 'Mai bpen chai',
    optionFour: 'Krap',
    answer: 'Mai bpen rai'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say how are you?',
    optionOne: 'Mai bpen rai',
    optionTwo: 'Mai chai',
    optionThree: 'Sa-baai dii mai',
    optionFour: 'Sa-baii',
    answer: 'Sa-baai dii mai'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say I am fine?',
    optionOne: 'Sa-baii dii',
    optionTwo: 'Sai',
    optionThree: 'Sa-baai dii mai',
    optionFour: 'Sa-baii',
    answer: 'Sa-baai dii mai'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say I am ok?',
    optionOne: 'Dii Gaw',
    optionTwo: 'Gaw dii',
    optionThree: 'Song',
    optionFour: 'Gao',
    answer: 'Gaw dii'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say I am not feeling well?',
    optionOne: 'Mai sa-baai',
    optionTwo: 'Sa-baai mai',
    optionThree: 'Krap',
    optionFour: 'Ha',
    answer: 'Mai sa-baai'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say what about you?',
    optionOne: 'Leko',
    optionTwo: 'Kun la',
    optionThree: 'Meko',
    optionFour: 'La kun',
    answer: 'Kun la'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say how is it going?, how is? or how was?',
    optionOne: 'Bpen yang',
    optionTwo: 'Bang yang',
    optionThree: 'Yang bang',
    optionFour: 'Bpen yang ngai baang',
    answer: 'Bpen yang ngai baang'
  },
  {
    question: "How to say what did you say? or what's that?",
    optionOne: 'Na-roi',
    optionTwo: 'Aroi',
    optionThree: 'Na arai',
    optionFour: 'A-rai na',
    answer: 'A-rai na'
  },
  {
    question: "How to say I don't know",
    optionOne: 'Arai',
    optionTwo: 'Ruu mai',
    optionThree: 'Na ruu',
    optionFour: 'Mai ruu',
    answer: 'Mai ruu'
  },
  {
    question: "How to say I don't understand",
    optionOne: 'Jaijai',
    optionTwo: 'Jai-kao',
    optionThree: 'Kaokao',
    optionFour: 'Mai kao-jai',
    answer: 'Mai ruu'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say I can speak Thai a little bit',
    optionOne: 'Puut paa-saa tai daai nit noi',
    optionTwo: 'Paa-saa tai yai',
    optionThree: 'Nit noi',
    optionFour: 'Mai',
    answer: 'Puut paa-saa tai daai nit noi'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say can you speak slowly please?',
    optionOne: 'Chai',
    optionTwo: 'Noi',
    optionThree: 'Puut chaa-chaa noi',
    optionFour: 'Chaa-chaa',
    answer: 'Puut chaa-chaa noi'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say how to say that in English?',
    optionOne: 'Chai',
    optionTwo: 'Ang-rit noi',
    optionThree: 'Puut paa-saa ang-grit yang-ngai',
    optionFour: 'Yang noi',
    answer: 'Puut paa-saa ang-grit yang-ngai'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to say see you later?',
    optionOne: 'Jer',
    optionTwo: 'Jer gan',
    optionThree: 'Gen jer',
    optionFour: 'Jer lii',
    answer: 'Jer gan'
  }
]
